Well, it's also emitting an event.
嗯，这里还有 "event" 的触发
So let's make sure it emits an event.
我们要确保这个 "event" 会被正常触发
So we'll say it emits event on enter.
所以我们要写 `it("emits event on enter")`
This will be an async function as well.
这里同样是一个 `async function`
And this will be the first time that we're testing to make sure a function emits an event
这是我们首次测试用于触发 "event" 的函数
and the syntax is going to look really similar to what we test for when we check to see if an error is fired.
它的语法和我们检查是否触发报错的测试很像
So we're gonna say await expect raffle dot enter raffle with value of raffle entrance fee dot two dot omit
所以我们写 `await expect(raffle.enterRaffle()).to.emit`
and this.to dot emit we get from During woful, these chime matches for emitting events
这个 ".to.emit" 我们要从 "ethereum-waffle" 的 "Chai mathcers" 的 "Emitting events" 部分获取
we can do a wait expect to emit,
我们可以执行 `await expect().to.emit`
and then the event that we're expecting to emit.
然后 "event" 就会被我们预期触发
So we're saying to omit the raffle contract to emit a raffle enter event.
所以我们说 `to.emit(raffle)` 触发的是 `"RaffleEnter"` 事件
We can copy this, try to test this in our terminal.
我们把这个复制下来，尝试在终端中测试一下
So we'll say hard hat. Test dash dash grep. Just put this in quotes.
也就是 `hh test --grep` 再把它放到引号内
And that passes as well. Great.
已经通过了，非常好